[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Morning.
&gt;&gt; 早上好
Welcome to Advances in TVMLKit.
欢迎来听“TVMLKit  的新改进”
I'm Trevor.
我叫 Trevor
I work in Localization, and
是本地化部门的员工
later, I'll be joined by my
我的同事  来自 tvOS 部门的
colleagues, Parry and Jeremy,
Parry 和 Jeremy 会在我
from tvOS.
之后发言
Today, we are really excited to
今天   我们很高兴
talk to you about three new
能和大家分享我们对 TVMLKit
advances that we have made.
做出的三大新改进
TVMLKit is Apple's developer
TVMLKit 是一个开发者框架
framework for building native
用于为 Apple TV 开发
applications for Apple TV using
原生应用程序  该框架
JavaScript and a markup language
可整合 JavaScript 和苹果自定义
that we call TVML.
标记语言 TVML
I am going to get things started
首先  演讲内容会谈到
by talking about right-to-left
对从右往左书写文字的支持
Then Parry will show us how to
第二位演讲者 Parry 会给大家
take advantage of new
展示如何应用模版中
optimizations in your templates,
一些新增的优化功能
to take performance to the next
来提升程序性能
Finally, Jeremy will show us
最后  Jeremy 会
some awesome new features that
给大家展示 Web 审查器中
you can use in the Web Inspector
新增了哪些很棒的新功能
to make debugging your
可帮你更便捷地
applications easier than ever.
给你的程序调试排错
So let's dive right in with
下面我们就开始  我先讲
right-to-left language support.
对从右往左书写文字的支持
Arabic and Hebrew are
tvOS 11 中新增了
newly-selectable languages in
两个可选语言  分别是阿拉伯语
tvOS 11.
和希伯来语
With over 400 million speakers
两门语言全球有超过4亿人使用
worldwide, this is a huge
如果你的 App
opportunity for you developers
能够在这两门语言环境下运行
to reach new audiences with your
就可让各位开发的应用触及到更多的用户
app.
要支持阿拉伯语和希伯来语
Hebrew different compared to
对比大家的应用程序目前
other languages you might be
已经支持的其他语言
supporting already is that they
区别在于阿拉伯语和希伯来语
are written and read from right
都是从右往左书写的
to left.
文字
Let's take a look at some
我先给大家看几个例子  展示一下
examples, so we can really
支持从右往左书写语言后
understand what that means for
大家的应用程序  看起来
your applications.
大概什么样
What you see here is our product
现在显示的是一个
template in a left-to-right
从左往右书写语言模式下
language, and it looks really
的产品模版  大部分人
normal to most of you in the
可能已经很熟悉这个
audience.
界面了
The text is aligned on the left,
文字左对齐
the content is flowing from the
内容排布顺序
left side of the screen to the
是从屏幕左边
right side of the screen.
排向屏幕右边
You see the focus is on the
优先选中的第一个按钮
first button, which is the
也是在屏幕的
left-most button.
最左边
So, when you take this template,
现在  如果我们选用这个模版
and you load it in a
然后在从右往左
right-to-left language, for
书写文字模式下加载
example, Hebrew, you see the
比如选择希伯来语  就可以看到
content is mirrored.
页面布局被左右翻转了
It is now flowing from the right
内容排布顺序会变成
side of the screen to the left
从屏幕右边
side of the screen.
排向屏幕左边
Our text is aligned to the
文字右对齐
right.
优先选中的  还是第一个按钮
button, but now you see it is on
但现在这一项位于
the other side.
屏幕右边了
Let's look at another example.
我们再看一个例子
Here, we have the catalogue
这是目录模版
template, and again, it looks
和刚才一样  如果你常用的语言
very normal and natural if you
是从左往右书写的
are a reader of a left-to-right
你可能会很熟悉这个界面
language.
很自然
So when you look at this same
但如果我们把同一个模版
example in a right-to-left
放到从右往左书写文字的
language, you see that the
模式下  我们会发现
content is mirrored again.
页面布局同样被翻转了
It is flowing from right to
内容变成从右往左
left.
排布
The first image is still the
第一张图片依然是沙漠
desert, but it is on the other
但现在这张图片显示在
side of the screen.
屏幕的另一边
So that is how these apps look
从右往左书写文字的模式下
in right-to-left languages, and
应用程序的界面看起来差不多就是这样
as you can see from these
从刚刚的演示中也可看到
examples, we've built the
我们把对相应语言的支持
support into TVMLKit.
都整合到了 TVMLKit 内部了
So when you're using the default
所以  只要你使用的是默认模版
templates, you get the support
你们的应用程序就可免费获得
for free in your apps.
对从右往左书写文字的优化支持
Now, supporting a right-to-left
而要让应用程序支持
language works the same way as
从右往左书写文字的显示模式
supporting any other languages
设置方法  和配置其他支持语言
in your app.
方法一样
You need to go into X code in
只需在 Xcode 中
your project settings, and in
进入 Project Setting 页面
the localizations, just add
可看到  在 localizations 下
Arabic or Hebrew, which are
目前新增了阿语和希语
supported languages.
我们按需添加即可
This is really key to make sure
把两种语言整合到 TVMLKit 中很重要
that TVMLKit knows when to
这样可确保 TVMLKit 在运行时
render these views at
能判断何时加载成
right-to-left at run time.
从右往左显示的界面
And for more coverage about
关于如何更好地
everything that it takes to
把应用程序本地化
support localizations in your
和更多相关详细信息
apps, including localizing
包括内容本地化
content and dealing with
和如何设置本地化的
formatters for dates and times,
时间日期格式  等等
I recommend checking out this
我推荐大家去听一个
year's talk, Localizing With X
今年的演讲  叫“Localizing With X
Code 9, which goes into much
Code 9” 那里会讲得
greater detail.
更详细一些
So the default templates work
好了  刚说了使用默认模版自带的
out of the box, but what if you
设置一键配置本地化  但如果程序里
have custom views, and you want
有自定义界面呢  如果你想
to customize the behavior beyond
实现一些模版中没有提供的
those templates.
显示效果呢
Well in tvOS 11 we have
在 tvOS 11 里
introduced three specific areas
我们新引入了三处可以
where you can customize layout,
自定义的领域  分别是页面布局
text alignment and images.
文字对齐方式和图片显示
Let's get started with layout.
我们首先说页面布局
Today, you might be customizing
目前我们自定义页面布局
your layout using tv-align, and
可能是靠分别设置
tv-position, and you are
tv-align 为 left(左)
probably using values of left
和设置 tv-position
and right.
为 right(右)
Well, for right-to-left
而对于从右往左书写
languages, left becomes left and
的文字  左是右
right becomes left, or something
右是左  是颠倒的
like that, so you need to take
这样我们再使用 left 和 right 就得格外小心
care to use the right direction.
很容易设置错方向
And for that, we've introduced
为此  我们引入了两个新的属性
leading and trailing.
叫 leading 和 trailing
Leading and trailing will
Leading 和 trailing
automatically resolve to the
会在程序运行时
corresponding values of left and
根据运行时的语言环境
right at run time, based on the
自动解析出与之适应的 left
running language of your
或者 right
application.
值
So, for example, if you have a
比方说  如果我们
style defined where you're
本来定义的样式里是
setting a tv-position to right
把 tv-position 设为 right
or tv-align to left, just
或者 tv-align 设为 left
replace those values with
现在  我们需要把后面的值
trailing and leading.
改为 leading 和 trailing
This is going to ensure that in
这样就可以确保
your left-to-right language,
在从左往右语言模式下
everything looks exactly the
页面显示效果还和原来一样
same, but in a right-to-left
但用从右往左语言模式加载后
language, content is flowing
内容依然能正确排布
For values of margin and
对于 margin 和 padding 的赋值
padding, we've introduced a
tvOS 11 引入了
brand-new media query in tvOS 11
一个全新的媒体查询属性
called Layout Direction.
叫作 Layout Direction (布局方向)
You might already be using media
大家可能已经
queries today for customizing
在通过使用媒体查询
your appearance for light and
来自定义调整页面明暗
These work just the same way.
这里也是一样的道理
Any styles that you define
在媒体查询内部
inside the media query will be
定义的样式  只在当前
active for that media query.
媒体查询中有效
So, here in our example, we have
如何应用  我来举一个例子
two styles defined, one in our
这个媒体查询定义了两个样式
LTR layout direction, left to
一个适用于从左往右(LTR)方向
right, and one in our RTL layout
另一个适用于从右往左(RTL)方向
And we take care to ensure that
这里设置 margin 时需要特意留心
any horizontal values are
依据语言书写方向
flipped according to the side
把水平向的左右外边距值
that they need to be on.
作相应对调
So here, in our example, our
在这个例子中
margin of 12 needs to be on the
我们给 margin 设置的值  12
correct side of the element.
就要写在正确的位置
So that's layout.
页面布局就说到这里
What about text direction?
那么文字对齐方向呢
So for alignment, you're used to
我们通常习惯的是  统一设置
using things like left, center
左对齐  居中  或者
and right.
右对齐
And when you look at the text on
而我们看这个屏幕上的文字
the screen, two kind of jump out
其中分别有两种显示方式
to you as a more natural
看起来比其他的更自然
presentation for a left-to-right
对于从左往右书写的文字
language, left alignment is
左对齐看起来自然
natural, and for a right-to-left
对于从右往左书写的文字
language, right alignment is
右对齐看起来自然
So, for that, we got with our
为此  我们专门
marketing team and thought
与市场团队碰头协商
really deeply about what kind of
思考了一下  究竟该如何
term could we use here, and we
命名这种对齐方式
came up with a new value for
最终决定  采用一个新的值
text alignment of natural.
叫作  自然对齐
Natural does just what you'd
自然对齐  效果和大家想象的
expect it to do.
差不多
It aligns a text naturally based
会根据大家应用程序的 UI 语言
on the UI language of your app.
对文字进行自然对齐
Easy stuff.
很简单
When it comes to images in your
下面再说应用程序中的图片显示
apps, the majority of the images
大部分应用程序内采用的图片
you have are universal.
都有一定普适性
They are appropriate to show for
不管页面如何布局  都可以
any layout direction.
正常显示
But in some cases, an image has
但在个别情况下
an implied directionality, like
某些图片会自带方向属性
this Chevron at the end of a
比如这个表单项后面的
list item.
V 形标记
In this case, it's really
这种情况下
important that the arrow is
就需要确保 V 形箭头
pointing in the correct
指向正确的方向
direction, otherwise it would
不然整个列表页面就会
look really weird and probably
令人困惑  看起来也
broken.
很奇怪
So there's two ways that you can
要在应用程序中做到这种效果
support these in your apps.
有两种方法
The first is for resource
一种是针对资源
images.
图片
Images that are coming from
对于来自应用程序
inside your application bundle
捆绑包内部的图片
can be specified in asset
可通过图片资源目录 (Asset Catalogs)
catalogs, which provide a really
来便捷地自定义
convenient way for customizing
图片显示方向
if the image is fixed for all
可设置在所有布局下
layout directions, can be
图片显示固定不变
graphically mirrored at runtime,
可像刚刚的 V 形标记
like our chevron, or if we
在运行时左右翻转显示
needed a dedicated asset for
或是给每门语言都指定一张
each language.
单独的图片
For images that are coming from
对于来自于服务器上的图片
your server, we have a brand new
我们引入了一个全新的属性
attribute that you can set on
可以用来定义图片元素
your image elements, called
这个属性就叫作
Source Set.
Source Set
Source Set allows you to
Source Set 可针对
identify a given URL for a given
某给定的布局方向设置一个
layout direction.
既定的图片 URL
What's great about Source Set is
Source Set 还有一个好处
that you can also use these for
就是  我们也可以通过
customizing your appearances for
设置 Source Set 属性来调整
light and dark.
明暗度
So here URL one will be loaded
在这个例子中  当布局方向是 LTR 时
when my layout direction is LTR,
就会载入 URL1 链接中的图片
and URL2 will be loaded when my
而当布局方向是 RTL 时
layout direction is RTL.
就会载入 URL2 图片
So this is a really concise way
通过这种方法
for you to just define a single
可以指定显示某张图片
image, and have the correct
运行时就会产出
thing happen at runtime.
正确的结果
So I'd like to see if we can
好了  现在看我们
take all of these pieces and put
能不能综合以上谈到的所有点
them together with a little
糅合在一个小程序里
sample app that I've been
我做了一个样本给大家
working on.
看看
So I've been working on an app
我之前一直在做一个应用程序
that lets me showcase the WWDC
来展示去年 WWDC
sessions from last year's
会上的演讲
conference, and I'd love to show
我现在跟大家分享一下
it to you now.
这个程序
So here you can see I have a
这个页面里  我们可以看到
grid of the past sessions, and
呈网格 (grid) 排列的往期演讲
at the top, I have a banner,
顶端我设置了一个横幅
where I have a featured session.
来进行置顶推荐
So before I want to support a
在正式让我的应用支持
right-to-left language in my
从右往左书写语言之前
app, I can do a few things
不去设置里添加本地化语言
without even adding a
也可以做一些此方面的
localization.
其他尝试
In the edit scheme, in our run
我们可以去 edit scheme 下
options, I can change the
在 run option 的下拉菜单中
application language from the
可以把应用程序
system language to a
的系统语言
right-to-left pseudolanguage.
改为从右往左的伪码
This lets me simulate what it's
设置后就可以模拟
going to be like in a
程序在从右往左
right-to-left language without
语言环境中的效果
having to change anything about
而项目本身不用做
my project.
任何改动
So now, when I build and run,
现在再编译并运行的话
you see our grid is now flowing
就能看到  网格布局变成了
from right to left.
从右往左排布
So because we're using a grid,
又因为我们使用了网格布局
we get that support for free
这些效果支持都是模版
from our template.
免费自带的
But because my banner was
但是因为我的横幅
custom, that I added with my own
是我自己自定义的样式
styles, looks like I still have
所以看起来这一部分还需要
some work to do.
我再去调试一下
So let's see if I can apply the
现在就让我们尝试使用
new API in tvOS 11 to fix these
tvOS 11 中的新 API 来调整
problems?
一下
The first thing that I'm going
首先我要做的一件事  就是
to do is check my style in my
检查我 TVML 里定义的样式
TVML and replace all of my
然后把所有规定死的
hard-coded references of left to
left  都替换成 leading
leading, which is the left side
在我所用的开发语言环境下
of the screen in my development
leading 也就是屏幕左侧 (left)
Similarly, I'll replace my
同样的  也把所有的
values of right with trailing.
right 都替换成 trailing
Now, when I build and run my
现在我们再编译并运行应用程序
app, hopefully we will have some
应该会看到改进后有什么
progress.
不同
So great, looks like our text
很好  看起来文字布局
has now flipped to the other
都翻到了屏幕另一边
side, and our play button is on
页面上的播放按钮
the right side of the screen,
也在正确的位置
but it seems like it's a little
但播放按钮看起来
bit too close to the edge.
离边框有点太近了
If I look at my style, my banner
查看一下代码样式就发现
play button lockup has a custom
我为 bannerPlayButtonLockup 单独
margin that is applied to the
设置了 margin  但定义的
right side of the element.
是元素的右边距
We need to make sure that margin
我们需要对此进行调整
is on the other side when we are
使得我们切换为从右往左语言模式后
running in right to left.
margin 赋值也相应对调
To save time, I added a snippet
为了节省时间  我这里插入
earlier that defines the two
我预先写好的一个片段
media queries for my Banner Play
这里为 bannerPlayButtonLockup 定义了
Button Lockup for LTR and RTL.
LTR 和 RTL  两个情况下的媒体查询
I'm going to move my definition
我只需把原先定义好的 margin
of the margin into the LTR, and
移动到 LTR 媒体查询下
in my RTL definition, I'm going
然后在 RTL 的媒体查询里
to swap the horizontal position
把右边距60调换成左边距
of that 60.
就行了
Now, when I build and run, looks
现在我们再编译并运行一下
like our play button has the
这下播放按钮的 padding 就看起来
right padding.
正常多了
So we are nearly there, but
现在页面布局完成得差不多了
looking at this app now, we can
但再看一下这个界面
kind of see that the text is on
我们发现  当横幅文字被移到
the other side.
右边后
It is a little hard to read with
背后正好和图片内容重合
that image right underneath it.
这样文字就不太容易阅读
So my designer gave me an
这时网页设计师给了我
alternate asset that I can use
一张左右翻转的图片
in my right-to-left languages,
可以用在从右往左布局的页面里
so I can add that to my project,
我就可以用图片资源目录 (Asset Catalogs)
since I'm using Asset Catalogs.
把这张图片加到项目里
Here, in my Asset Catalogue, I
在我的这个图片资源目录里
have a single image defined for
当前只为横幅指定了
my banner, and then in the
一张图片
attribute inspector, I can
我可以在 Attribute Inspector 里
change the direction from fixed
把布局方向从 fixed (固定) 改为
to both.
both (双向)
This now gives me a well where I
这样设置后  就会出现预留空位
can drop the asset that should
把需要在从右往左布局中使用的
be used in our right-to-left
左右翻转的图片  拖拽到空位上
language.
就可以了
So I'll drop that in place and
现在我就拖拽过来
build and run my app one last
最后再编译并运行一下我的应用程序
time.
这就是调试结果了
With just a few small changes,
只需进行一些很小的改动
our app is now ready to support
我们的应用程序就可以完美支持
right to left.
从右往左布局了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So as you saw, with just a few
总结一下  就像大家所见
small changes to our app,
只需对程序进行一些很小的改动
because the default templates
大部分工作都可以由默认模版中
give us the support for free, we
自带的免费技术支持来完成
can have an app that fully
很轻松  就能让我们的程序
supports a right-to-left
支持从右往左书写文字
language, with very few changes
我们需要做的编程改动
needed from us.
非常少
We also have a really powerful
同时  从右往左的伪码也是一个
tool in the right-to-left
非常强大的工具
pseudolanguage, that allows us
我们可以在不懂任何
to simulate the effects of a
从右往左书写语言的情况下
right-to-left layout without
通过伪码模拟  查看程序
having to read a right-to-left
在从右往左布局下的
language.
显示效果
Now, one last note, if you're
还有再多说一点  如果你的应用
using custom views in your
要使用自定义试图
application, we have a system of
我们的 AutoLayout Engine 里
constraints in auto layout
还有一系列约束 (constraint)
engine that is a really powerful
这些约束  功能非常强大
tool to take care of layout for
可以帮助你们优化从右往左书写
right to left languages.
语言模式下的布局
We also have an API effective
我们还有一个基于 API 的
layout direction, which will
布局方向属性  返回的结果
return to you if you are in a
可以显示运行时
left-to-right or a right-to-left
你是在一个从左往右
layout direction at run time,
还是从右往左的布局
which is really useful for doing
在做动画帧的屏幕
things like frame math in an
自适应运算时  这个功能
animation.
会很有用
For more in-depth coverage about
了解从右往左书写语言的布局的
all the things, and nuances for
更多细节  或是
supporting right-to-left
想要深入了解相关信息
languages, I recommend checking
我推荐大家去听去年的
out last year's talks,
两场相关演讲
Internationalization Best
Internationalization Best
Practices, and What's New In
Practices 和 What's New In
International User Interfaces.
International User Interfaces
I can't wait to see your apps
我迫不及待在今年秋天的时候
supporting right-to-left
能看到你们的应用程序
languages later this fall.
开始支持从右往左的语言布局
Now, here is Parry, with
下面有请 Parry
template optimizations.
为大家介绍模版优化项目
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Trevor.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Trevor
Hi! I'm Parry.
大家好  我是 Parry
I'm going to walk you through
下面我将给大家介绍
some of the enhancements we made
我们对模版进行的一些改进
to our templates that is going
这些改进将会提高你们
to improve the performance of
应用程序的运行性能
your app, both in terms of time
既可以优化响应时间
and memory.
又可以减少内存占用
If you worked with TVMLKit apps
如果你用 TVMLKit 做过应用程序
before, you might have noticed
那么也许已经注意到
that the performance of a
当我们试图往模版里
template degrades as you try to
添加更多内容的时候
add more content into it.
模版性能会逐渐降低
Let me illustrate with an
让我用一个例子给大家演示
example.
一下
So I'm working with Trevor on
我和 Trevor 一起
our sample WWDC app, and I'm
在开发这个 WWDC 的样本程序
trying to enhance it to add all
我希望这个应用程序能搭载
the sessions from the past,
所有的往期演讲
instead of just the last year's
而不是只有去年的
sessions.
演讲
We are keeping a simple design
我们依然维持简洁的页面设计
with a grid to showcase all the
用网格 (grid) 来展示所有
sessions.
演讲
Each session being represented
每个演讲都由一个 lockup 元素来代表
by a lockup composed of an image
其中包括一张图片
and a title.
和一个文字标题
Now, you can imagine that there
大家可以想象  要展示的全部内容
are thousands of these sessions
会包括上千个像这样的
to show.
视频
So in a typical scenario like
所以一般针对这种典型情况
this, you don't want to show all
我们不希望这个页面  一上来
your content up front, because
就显示出所有内容
A, it is going to take a long
因为首先  一下全部显示出来
time to load, and B, it might
加载时间太长  而第二
not even be possible, because
很有可能根本无法一下全部显示
your servers might not support
那还要看你的服务器是否能够
that.
支持
But instead, you paginate your
所以我们就需要给数据进行分页 (paginate)
data.
处理
You start off with something
可以先显示一小部分
small, let's say about 500
比方说 500 个项目
items, and then you keep adding
然后等用户滚动到
to it, as the users scroll
接近内容末尾时
through the end of your content.
再不断加载下一部分内容
Now, we did a bit of performance
我们针对这种情形做了
analysis for such a scenario,
一个性能分析
and this is what it looks like.
结果差不多如图
What you see in this graph is
这张图上显示的是
the time it took to build the
编译一个含有一定数量
template with a certain number
项目的模版  需要多长时间
of items, and what you see on
我们可以看到  这张图里
the x axis is the number of
位于 X 轴上的数值
items in the template, and what
代表着模版中项目的数量
you see on the y is the time it
而 Y 轴数值  代表显示出这么多项目
took to reach there.
所需要的时间
And as you can see, it's an
我们从图中可以看出
exponential curve.
花费时间呈指数增长
Meaning that it takes longer to
也就是说  随着模版
add the same number of items to
体量增大  要加载同样多
the template as the size of the
数量的项目  就需要花费
template grows.
更多的时间
But why is that?
这又是为什么呢
Well, one of the major factors
一个很重要的影响因素
is the size of the document
就是这些模版里
object model back in these
文档对象模型 (DOM) 的
templates.
大小
The problem is two-fold.
这个问题有两方面
On one hand, you have the
一方面是
parsing overhead.
存在多余的模板语法解析
First, in your JavaScript, when
首先  是在你的 JavaScript 里
you parse your data into the
要把数据解析到 DOM 树里
DOM, so when the DOM size
这样  当 DOM 树越来越大
increases it takes longer to add
要添加新的东西进去
more stuff to it, and then when
就需要花更多的时间
TVMLKit has to parse a DOM in
然后  TVMLKit 还得解析 DOM
order to calculate out
来计算出显示布局
information, like cell sizes,
所需信息  比如内容格大小
line spacing, even scrolling
行距  甚至滚动
offsets.
偏移量
All the things that make your
上述这些参数   会让你们的
TVMLKit app look beautiful.
TVMLKit 程序界面看起来非常漂亮
But as you can imagine, as the
但可以想象的是
size of the DOM increases, it
DOM 树越大  完成这些
takes longer to perform these
计算所需的时间
operations.
就越长
And on the other hand, you have
而另一方面  DOM 树越来越大
an increasing memory pressure
对内存的压力也会越来越大
because of an increasing DOM
这就会整体拖慢
size, which slows down your app
你应用程序的响应
as a whole.
时间
So to solve these problems, in
为了解决响应时间和内存占用问题
tvOS 11, we've come up with a
在 tvOS 11 中  我们引入了一个全新的
brand new paradigm of defining
模版定义范式
templates using prototype and
新方法采用原型 (Prototype)
data binding which is going to
加数据绑定 (Data Binding) 来构建模版
significantly reduce the size of
此方法可以显著降低 DOM 树大小
your DOM, hence improving your
从而提高大家
app's performance, and on top of
应用程序的性能  除此之外
that, we've added APIs to
我们还增加了一些 API
support pagination.
来支持数据分页
Let's look at these in more
下面我们详细讨论
detail.
一下
In order to understand what a
为了方便大家理解原型
prototype is, I'm going to walk
到底是什么  我先给大家
you through a typical template
讲一下  一个典型的模版
building process.
构建过程
You start off with the data from
最开始  在我们手上的
your servers, and an empty shell
是你服务器上的数据  和一个模版
of a template.
的空壳
In our case, it's a grid.
针对我们这个程序  是个网格模版
And in your JavaScript, you go
然后根据 JavaScript
through each one of these
我们需要把
objects, and you can word them
JavaScript 里的对象都逐一
into their corresponding TVML
翻译成相对应的 TVML
markup.
语言
In our case, it's a lockup.
在我们这个应用里  翻成 lockup
Once you've done that, you parse
做完这一步之后
that into a DOM, and that is
再把这些都转化成 DOM 树
when TVMLKit starts producing
然后 TVMLKit 就可以开始
the user interface for it.
生成 UI 了
But if you look closely, you'll
但如果我们仔细研究一下代码
see that all of these lockups,
就会发现  这些 lockup 之间
they look very similar.
相似度非常高
In fact, the only thing that is
实际上这些 lockup 之间  唯一不同的
different between them are the
地方  就是它们各自
values that are coming from the
从数据中解析来的值
Once you remove these values,
如果我们去除这些值
what you end up with is an
剩下的就是一些
identical looking lockup that
完全一样的 lockup
has all the information that
其中任何一个  所包含的信息
TVMLKit needs to compute that
就已经足够 TVMLKit 预先计算出
layout up front.
如何布局页面了
So it turns out, you don't need
所以  其实我们并不需要
all of these lockups, you just
写这么多个 lockup
need one of them.
写一个就够了
And that's what we call a
而提炼出的这个骨架  就是一个
prototype.
原型了
So a prototype is a TVML schema
所以简单说  原型就是个针对
for your data objects that
数据对象的 TVML 语言纲要
TVMLKit can use to compute the
TVMLKit 可利用这一纲要
layout up front, and then at
预先计算布局  然后在
runtime, it can combine it with
运行时  再和数据
the data to author the DOM for
进行结合  自动帮你创建 DOM 树
you, but only the parts that it
但只解析它所需要的那一部分
needs when it needs it.
且只在需要的时候才解析
So the DOM size remains concise,
这样就可以控制 DOM 树较小
and independent of your data set
且大小独立  不随数据变多而增长
Now, you can imagine a template
当然  如果一个模版里
with just a prototype would be
只有原型  还不完整
incomplete, because you also
我们还需要给模版
need to provide data.
提供数据
But on top of that, you also
但除了提供数据
need to provide a link between
我们还需要把模版
your template and your data.
和数据关联起来
This is how TVMLKit can make
这样 TVMLKit 才能
sense of what your data is, and
解析你的数据
complete the template for you.
并且帮你完成模版构建
And you specify that using data
这一关联过程就要靠数据绑定
bindings.
来完成
There are three ways that you
要在 tvOS 11 里
can bind data to your templates
给模版绑定数据  一共有
in tvOS 11.
三种方法
First, you can bind a source and
首先  可以给一个元素的来源
attribute of an element.
绑定属性
In this example, the source
这个例子里  就给
attribute of the image element,
图像元素的来源属性
which is bound to the URL
绑定了数据中的
property of the data.
URL 属性
You can also bind text content
我们还可以对一个元素的文字内容
of an element, like in this
进行绑定
case, binding the text content
这个例子里  就给 title 元素的
of the title element, with the
文字内容 (textContent) 绑定了
title property in the data.
数据中的 title 属性
And finally, you can bind items
最后  我们还可以把一个组件
of a section using the items
中的某些项目绑定
binding.
对象
With this, you can bind the
我们可以将组件中的
trial DOM elements of the
试验 DOM 元素
section with an array of
和一系列对象进行
objects.
绑定
So in a nutshell, data binding
所以简单说  数据绑定
provides the association between
就是一种链接  用来关联
a TVML property and a data
TVML 属性和数据属性
property.
这种关联  可以在 TVML 里
it directly in TVML using a
利用一个绑定属性
binding attribute.
来直接指定
Now, when it comes to providing
说到为 TVMLKit 提供数据
data to TVMLKit, you can do that
我们还可以在 JavaScript 里
in your JavaScript using a new
用 DataItem 来实现这一点
property you've introduced on a
这是我们对 DOM 元素
DOM element called Data Item.
引入的一个新属性
Here is an example.
我来举个例子
You parse your JSON into
我们读取 JSON
JavaScript Objects, then you
将数据转换为 JavaScript 对象
attach it to the section element
然后再用 DataItem 属性
using the data item property.
把该对象关联到组件元素上
Now, let's move on to
好了  我们接下来说
pagination.
分页
In tvOS 11 we have introduced a
在 tvOS 11 里  我们引入了
new event called Needs More that
一个新事件叫作 Needs More
you can use to conveniently
用这个事件  我们可以很方便地
implement pagination.
对数据进行分页
This event gets invoked as the
当用户滚动到
users scroll toward the end of
接近页面内容末尾时
your content, and you get it on
就会触发这一事件  可应用范围
list, shelf, grid, and even
包括 list  shelf  grid
stack template, so it's very
甚至 stackTemplate
versatile, and you can use it in
用途广泛  且几乎可以应用到
almost any template.
任何模版上
However, if you're using
但要注意的是
pagination on a data bound
如果要在数据绑定模板中
template, you need to create
进行分页  还需要给数据
observable objects for your
创建可观察对象
This is how TVMLKit can observe
这样 TVMLKit 才能观察监听到
the changes that you make in the
你对数据做出的改动
data, and push those updates to
并在发生变动后  主动更新
the user interface.
UI 界面
Let's take an example of how to
让我们看一个   如何创建
create these observable objects.
这些可观察对象的例子
So you start off just the same.
开头的地方都一样
You parse your JSON into
解析 JSON 成为一个
JavaScript objects, but then you
JavaScript 对象  但接下来
go through each one of these
要遍历每一个对象
objects and map them into a data
把它们映射为一个
item class.
DataItem 类
This is something that they've
这一项也是 tvOS 11
also introduced in tvOS 11 that
里介绍过的  本身
has an observer pattern built
自带观察者模式
You construct the data item
我们创建 dataItem 时
class with an optional type, in
把它设置为可选类型
case you want to have multiple
这样万一你希望模版中
prototypes in your template, and
有多个原型  也可以
a required identifier that
还要规定识别码
TVMLKit uses to push those
TVMLKit 可以利用这个识别码
updates to the user interface
更高效地把更新推到
efficiently.
UI 上
And once you have all of these
映射完成后
objects mapped, you want to wrap
还要把这个 DataItem 类
them up in another data item,
包在另一个 sectionDataItem 里
and that is what you attach to
最终才是  把这个 sectionDataItem 关联到
the element.
元素上
Let's take an example of how to
我们举个例子来看看如何
handle Needs More.
处理 Needs More
Now, Needs More is just like any
Needs More 和其他事件
other event.
一样
So you listen for it by using
我们可以用
the Add Event Listener method on
Add Event Listener 方法
a DOM element, and you provide a
来监听一个 DOM 元素
function that would have kind of
再提供一个函数
a similar implementation to what
这个函数执行起来
you would have when creating the
和新构建一个模板
template.
差不多
So you fetch the data from your
从数据库提取数据
servers, map those objects into
映射为 DataItem 类
data item, but finally, instead
但最后一步
of attaching those data items
不是把这些 DataItem
directly to the element, you
直接关联到元素上
append to the existing elements.
而是插入到已有元素的末尾
And once you've done that, you
完成以上这些操作之后 And once you've done that, you
call Touch Property Path Method
再对 DataItem 类调用
on the data item class to push
Touch Property Path Method
your updates to the user
把你数据更新推到
interface.
UI 上
Now, let's put all of these
现在我们综合以上讲到的
pieces together in a demo.
用程序给大家示范一下
So as Trevor was doing his demo,
刚刚 Trevor 给大家演示的时候
I actually went in and
我在他样本程序
implemented pagination in the
的脚本里添加了代码  进行了
sample app.
数据分页
So why don't we start from
不如就从这里开始讲吧
So I am going to take you
我们直接在代码中
directly to the part where I
找到相应的
construct the stack document,
构建 stackDocument 的部分
and the event I'm handling is
我要处理的事件  就关联
directly on the stack element
在 stackElement 元素
itself.
上
And as you can see, what I'm
大家可以看到
doing is fetching the next batch
这里我先抓取了下一批
of assets that I want to push in
想要推到模版上的数据
the template, creating
读取返回的 JSON
JavaScript objects from the JSON
将数据转换为
that is returned, and then
JavaScript 对象
recalling populateGrid to add it
再调用 populateGrid 函数  把对象
to the template.
加到模版里
Let's see what populateGrid
populateGrid 这个函数是做什么的呢
Now, at this point, I haven't
目前我创建的模版
converted my templates using
还没有使用新的原型
prototype and data binding.
加数据绑定方法
So what you see here is very
所以可能大家看着代码觉得很
familiar.
熟悉
You would probably already know
大家看一眼  也许就知道这个函数
what is happening here.
是要做什么
I start off with an empty grid
首先这里  我添加了一个空网格
and I map all of my objects into
然后遍历此批数据中的对象
the corresponding TVML markup,
把它们都用 TVML 标记语言表述
which is a lockup in this case,
这个例子里用的是 lockup
and finally I parse all of those
最后把所有这些 lockup
lockups directly into the DOM.
都直接解析到 DOM 里
Now, before I go ahead and
我稍后会用新方法
convert it into a data bound
把这些转换成数据绑定模板
template, let's run this app,
但在那之前  我们先运行一次
just to get a feel of what
体验一下  在 TVMLKit 里
pagination looks like in
执行分页加载
TVMLKit.
是什么样
So as you can see, it starts off
我们可以看到  刚打开时
just the same.
没什么区别
But notice as I scroll toward
但注意看  当我滚动到
the end of this grid, the index
接近这个网格末尾的时候
bar on the right side jumps
右侧的索引条
back, and that is because we are
会向上跳回  这是因为
adding all those items as we
滚动接近末尾时  程序会自动
approach toward the end.
在网格末尾插入新的项目
So great, our pagination works.
好  现在分页实现了
But let's go back and complete
让我们回过头  做完这个例子
this example by converting our
再用新引入的原型加
templates to using prototype and
数据绑定的方法  改写优化一下
data binding.
这个模版
Now, as you might have imagined,
跟大家想的差不多
all the changes that I need to
要把现有模版
make in order to convert it into
转换成数据绑定模板
a data bound template are in
我所需要做的全部改动
this one function, populateGrid.
都在 populateGrid 这一个函数里
And the first thing I want to do
我首先要做的就是
is, instead of adding a simple
对比原来单纯地添加空网格
grid, I want to add prototypes
我需要添加一些原型
and a bound grid, like this.
和一个绑定网格  就像这样
The next thing I want to do is,
接下来的一步
instead of mapping all of these
我不需要逐一把这些对象
objects into their markup, I
都映射到标记语言
want to map them into observable
而是需要用 DataItem 类把它们
objects using data item class.
映射为可观察对象
Just like that.
像这样
And finally, instead of creating
最后一步  我也不需要
all of these markups into the
把这些标记语言都直接
DOM itself, I want to append my
读到 DOM 里  我只需把
created data items into the
新创建的 DataItem 插入到
existing ones.
已有 DataItem 的末尾
Like so. So now that we have all
像这样  现在我们已经完成了
of these pieces in, let's re-run
所有的优化改写  再运行一下
this app and check it out.
看看效果
Now, right out of the box, one
应用程序一启动
thing that I have noticed is
我们就可以注意到
that it loads faster, even with
加载速度更快了  尽管
such a small subset of content
启动时只加载了
that I'm loading up front, it
很少一部分内容
takes less time to load.
也能体会到速度增快
And as I scroll toward the
而当我向下滚动时
bottom, it has flawless
可看到程序性能
performance with buttery smooth
表现完美  滚动效果流畅
scrolling.
顺滑
It is quite addictive, I could
滚起来还挺上瘾的
scroll all day actually.
我能玩一天
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So let's do a quick recap of
让我们回顾一下
what you saw.
讲过的内容
What you saw is how to implement
我们刚刚讲了  如何运用原型
your templates using a better
和数据绑定这一更优化的
paradigm of prototypes and data
模版定义范式来构建你的
binding.
模版
That is going to reduce your DOM
优化后可以降低 DOM 树
size, and make your apps
大小  提高应用程序
perform, and how to implement
性能  我们还讲了如何利用
pagination conveniently using
Needs More 事件  便捷地
Needs More event.
对数据进行分页
Now, there is one more thing
在我结束前  还想给大家
that I want to recreate before I
重现一个测试结果
Remember this graph that I
还记得我之前给大家
showed you earlier, about how
展示的这张图吗  显示了
long it takes to build a
构建一个含有一定数量
template to a certain number of
项目的模版  需要多长时间
After re-implementing our
我们如例子中演示的  用原型
example with prototypes and data
加数据绑定的新方法  重新构建了模版
binding, we re-ran this test,
之后重做了一次性能分析
and we found there were more
结果显示  采用新方法后
than 50% reduction in the time
编译同样的模版所需的时间
it took to build these
比起原先  缩短了
templates.
超过50%
So we were really happy with it.
这个结果让我们很满意
So I encourage you to check out
所以我鼓励大家都去看一下
these APIs, and try them out in
这些 API  并且在你们的应用程序中
your apps, and see what you can
试验一下  看看你能从中
gain from them.
收获什么
I am going to hand it over to
我就说到这里  下面由
Jeremy now, to talk all about
Jeremy 来给大家讲
Web Inspector.
Web 审查器 (Web Inspector)
Thank you.
谢谢大家
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you Parry.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Parry
Hi everyone, my name is Jeremy.
大家好  我的名字是 Jeremy
And today I am here to tell you
今天我想和大家讲讲
how you can achieve happiness
在 Web 审查器 (Web Inspector) 帮助下
when you do TVMLKit development
进行 TVMLKit 开发时
with the help of Web Inspector.
如何在开发中获得幸福
Now, we have seen amazing demos
我们已经看过 Parry 和 Trevor
from Parry and Trevor, trying to
尝试开发 WWDC 样本程序
build up a simple WWDC app.
的精彩示范
And at this point in time, it is
程序开发到这一步  已经
fairly capable.
比较能干了
It supports RTL, so it can be
目前的程序可以支持 RTL  因此
localized immediately to
可以一键本地化  设置成
right-to-left languages.
从右往左书写语言模式
And it uses data binding and
构建模版时还使用了数据绑定
prototypes, so you could scroll
加原型方法  所以可以流畅地
forever, and not stop.
滚动  不会卡住等待加载
Now, as luck would have it, just
但好巧不巧  就在
a few days before we are ready
我们准备上线的前几天
to ship, the designer comes over
设计师突然跑过来
and hands us this mock-up.
给了我们这么一个版面设计
He gives you a thumbs up and
他竖起大拇指  跟你说
says, "this should be easy to
这个调整一下  应该很简单
Now, we all know that is not
我们都知道实际调整起来  没那么
true.
简单
And I empathize with that, and I
对此我可以说非常感同身受
can hear all the inward groaning
你们心里的那些抱怨声
in all your bellies.
我也都能听见
So let's try to articulate this
让我们一起看一下开发周期
feeling that we have by looking
看看尤其针对这种 UI 调整
at the development cycle,
要做哪些具体步骤
especially when it comes to
借此试图细数一下
updating user interface.
到底这哪些点非常恼人
The very first thing you have to
这个 UI 调整  首先要做的
do is that you have to formulate
就是预估出来所有需要调整的
speculative fixes, guess well as
部分  还要猜测  为实现目标 UI
to what it involves to fix the
具体需要做哪些
UI.
改动
Is the margin one pixel to the
margin 是往右还是往左
right, or to the left?
移动一像素
Once you have formulated all
等你预估完所有需要
your fixes, you have to go
调整的部位  还要
through this tedious Build and
再反复编译并运行
Run cycle.
来调试
You build and run in X code,
我们需要在 Xcode 里编译并运行
wait for the app to start, look
等着应用启动  看一眼
at the changes, is this right or
改动后的效果  对不对
not?
如果不对  还得
through that over and over again
再一遍遍地重复这个过程
until it is right.
直到结果正确
Consequently, because of that,
然后因为这个冗长的过程
there is a huge loss of context.
中间会丢失大量上下文
You forgot where you were and
开发者很容易就会沉浸在细微末节里
what you're trying to fix,
而忘记最终想要的目标效果
simply because there is this
因为在调试过程中
huge time gap between the
从你对代码做出改动
changes you make, and seeing
到看到屏幕上的运行效果
them on the screen.
间隔时间实在太久
So how amazing would it be if
所以  如果有一样东西
there was something that could
能帮我们解决这些问题
help us fix all these problems?
那该有多好
Seasoned web developers out
一些经验丰富的 Web 开发者
there already use Web Inspector,
已经在使用 Web 审查器的
with all these amazing features.
这些强大的功能了
It is about visual debugging,
包括可视化调试排错
local and session storage
对 LocalStorage
introspection, even performance
和 SessionStorage 的内省  甚至
analysis for JavaScript.
对 JavaScript 进行性能分析
And today, tvOS only supports
当前的 tvOS 在 TVMLKit 里
this small subset of features in
只支持这一小部分针对
TVMLKit for Web Inspector.
Web 审查器的功能
So today I am really pleased to
今天  我很高兴能宣布
announce that in tvOS 11 we are
在 tvOS 11 中  我们会增加
adding support for the remaining
对 Web 审查器其余
few bits of Web Inspector.
几项功能的支持
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; So to get us started, let's
&gt;&gt; 我们首先讲一下
talk about visual debugging.
可视化调试排错 (Visual Debugging)
Your TVML app is a document that
你的 TVML 应用  是一个
is represented as a DOM, and to
以 DOM 来代表的文件  为了
visualize that, Web Inspector
可视化这些 Web 审查器
has the Elements tab.
设有 Elements 标签页
It shows a tree of all the nodes
这里树状显示了全部节点
that TVML uses to render UI on
TVML 就用这些节点
the screen.
来渲染 UI
So the very first thing we did
我们首先做的一项工作
is we wanted to eliminate all
就是我们希望能完全避免
guesswork as to the things you
猜测  而直接定位到需要
actually have to fix, and that
调整的部分  要实现
is through the usage of
这一点  就应用了
visualization.
可视化
If you move your mouse slowly
如果将鼠标缓慢
over the nodes in your tree, we
移动到树中节点上方
would highlight the
Web 审查器会自动
corresponding views on the
在屏幕上高亮与节点对应的
screen itself.
UI 图形区域
We even give you information
甚至会提供
about its dimensions, and its
尺寸信息  和相关联
elements that it is associated
的都有哪些元素
with.
现在我们准确定位了需要改动的
node you have to fix, you can
那个节点  就可以
edit the individual XML
针对这个节点
structure of that node itself.
编辑它的 XML
Any changes you make will
期间你做出的任何改动
validate before rendering UI for
都会在渲染 UI 前生效
Now, if you don't want to deal
如果你不想改动
with XML, and you just want to
XML  而只是想
reorder nodes on the screen, you
重新排列屏幕上的节点  这点
can also do that.
也可以做到
It is as simple as dragging the
很简单  只需拖拽节点
nodes between the areas that you
拖动到你期望的目标位置
want it to go and then the
屏幕界面上会自动
screen updates itself.
显示出相应的更新
For developers that want to see
也有一些开发者  想在不同
their applications in a
明暗度下
different light, light or dark,
查看 UI 效果  亮或者暗
you can change the attributes on
这点可以在模版上直接
the template itself.
改动属性
In fact, you can change any
实际上  全部节点的
attributes on any nodes you
所有属性  都可以修改
And finally, all these changes
最后一点  我们做出的
that you have made, you are able
所有这些改动  都可以
to copy it out and paste it in
复制出来  然后随意粘贴进
any file you want.
任何文件
Now that we've seen how we can
现在我们看过了如何
change the layout itself, let's
改变页面布局  我们再
look at the properties we use to
看一下屏幕上渲染 UI
render UI on the screen.
所需要用到的属性
Web Inspector allows you now to
现在 Web 审查器可让我们
look at the individual rules
查看每一个节点
that are attached to individual
所关联的对应规则
nodes, so you can see every
所以现在我们可以查看
single rule that is used to
渲染全部节点所用的
render them on the screen.
每一条规则
These are arranged in a cascade
这些都按照层叠顺序
ordering, rules that matter the
来排序  权重最大的
most are right at the top, and
那些规则  显示在最上面
things that it overrides is
它们覆盖的那些规则
loaded right at the bottom.
被排在最底端
Media queries are able to be
媒体查询也可以
visualized as well, so you'll be
被可视化  所以我们也可以
able to see the individual rules
查看特定媒体查询
that correspond to specific
所对应的
media queries, so for example,
特定规则  举个例子
you have rules for LTR, you will
若有针对 LTR 的规则  也可以
be able to see them grouped that
看到相应规则被归类显示
way too.
了
Finally, the Web Inspector
最后  Web 审查器
allows you to look at the
还可以让我们查看
default rules that ship with the
框架本身自带的
framework itself, so that
默认规则
totally takes guesswork out of
这样一来  要知道做出
figuring out what is the default
一个完美漂亮的 UI 成品
rules that you have to change in
还需要改动哪些默认规则
order to make your UI look like
也完全不需要靠开发者自己
the beauty it is.
来猜测了
And of course, with all these
当然  显示出来
rules that are displayed, we
这么多的规则  我们
will also show you the coalesced
也会提供一个合并
version of it.
的版本
These are the exact styles that
屏幕上渲染 UI 时
the framework uses to render UI
用的就是这些
on the screen.
样式了
In Web Inspector, there is a
在 Web 审查器里  还有
reload button, and now, by
一个重新加载 (Reload) 按钮  现在
hitting the reload button, you
只要点击这个按钮
are able to restart the entire
就可以重启整个
JavaScript context without going
JavaScript 执行上下文  不需要
through Build and Run over and
再通过反复编译并运行来调试
over again.
程序
So with that, I'd love to show
讲完这些  我想用一个
you a demo of all these features
演示实例  给大家展示一下
that I've talked about.
刚刚所说的功能
So I have gone ahead and gotten
现在我已经事先准备
the project ready, and updated
好了项目  也更新了 UI
the UI, but the last bit to do
最后要做的就是
is to check if it accurately
检查程序是否可以
supports RTL.
完美支持 RTL
There we go.
好了
And once again, we are going to
我们现在要再次应用
use the thing that Trevor taught
前面 Trevor 教给我们的方法
us, by going to the scheme, and
去 scheme 下
changing the system language to
把应用程序的系统语言
right-to-left pseudolanguage.
改为从右往左的伪码
Let's build and run.
编译并运行一下
All right.
好了
As we can see, everything looks
如大家所见  整体看起来
kind of right, except the banner
还不错  除了页面上方的横幅
right up there, which we haven't
我们还没来得及为 RTL
optimized for RTL.
做优化
So instead of going through that
那么接下来的调试  我们就不需要
Build and Run cycle that Trevor
像 Trevor 那样  反复编译并运行
was doing, let's try to do it in
而是试图通过
Web Inspector.
Web 审查器来做
The way to do this is that you
讲下具体操作方法  我们先
start Safari, there is a develop
打开 Safari   可以看到我已经
menu that I've already enabled,
启用了开发者工具菜单
and you go into Simulator, and
点进去  找到 Simulator
inspect the app that you want to
然后审查你想要调试的应用
look at.
程序
So Web Inspector starts up, and
这就打开了 Web 审查器
let's get going.
可以开始调试了
So we want to change specific
现在我们想要改动
user interface elements on the
屏幕上的几个 UI 元素
screen, and we can see that the
我们可以看到  这里的
title, the subtitle, and the
标题  副标题  和
button needs some work.
按钮  都需要调整
With Web Inspector, you can
用 Web 审查器  我们可以
easily drill down to the exact
轻松定位到这些元素
nodes that it is related to by
所对应的节点
moving the mouse, and you can
只要移动鼠标  就可以看到
see that things start getting
节点对应的元素被
highlighted.
高亮了
So let's go quickly to the title
我们现在快速地找到标题
and change it.
来进行调整
Now, Web Inspector shows you all
找到后  Web 审查器会显示出
the rules that correspond to
这个节点所对应的
this node, and all we need to do
所有规则  我们现在只需
is hunt for this pesky bottom
在规则中找到这个恼人的
left that should be actually
bottom-left   把它改为
bottom viewing.
bottom-leading
And as I type, observe what
大家注意看  我边打字
happens on the simulator screen
模拟屏幕上会产生什么
itself.
变化
Boom, it updates automatically
你看  屏幕显示自动更新了
without needing to build and
不需要我们再去编译并运行
run.
响应非常快  如果有人
that missed it, let's try to do
没看到  我们再来
it again for the subtitle
对副标题进行一下
itself, and it's the same steps.
改动  一样的步骤
Locate the element you want, and
定位到你想改动的元素
change the style associated with
改动相关联的样式
There we go.
好了
Now, let's quickly update the
我们也把播放按钮
Play button as well, so it's on
快速地修改一下  让它
the right side of the screen.
显示在正确的位置
For that, we are going to change
我们需要把所有的 right
all right to trailing.
都改为 trailing
Trailing. And of course, like
拼一下 trailing  当然
Trevor did as well, we need a
就像 Trevor 之前做的  为了设置
special media created for its
正确的 margin  还需单独
margins, because it is different
创建媒体查询  因为 RTL 语言模式下
when in RTL language.
数据要写在不同位置
So I am going to copy margin
所以我来复制一下 margin
Paste it over.
粘贴过去
And change all that.
这里再改一下
And there we have it.
然后就好了
Now, since all these changes
我们做的这些改动
were made to the author style
都是在作者样式表上
sheet itself, which is contained
而作者样式表是包含在
in the style attribute, the
样式属性
style tag, we are going to copy
样式标签下  我们把这些都复制
this out.
下来
In order to verify, we are going
为了核对  我们把这些
to paste it into our TVML
都粘贴到我们的 TVML
document.
文档里
So here we go.
好了
And then instead of building and
然后这次不用编译并运行
run, we're just going to hit
我们可以直接点击
Reload.
重新加载
And there we have it.
就好了
Everything works correctly
一切运行正常
[applause].
[掌声]
Let's go back to the slides.
我们回到幻灯片
So what we are seeing is a very
大家刚刚看到了  这种方法
quick way to figure out user
可以快速定位 UI 中的问题
interface issues and fix them.
并对其进行调整
What we've done is we have
应用起来的具体步骤
looked for the particular nodes
是先找到具体
that it has affected, edited
受影响的节点  对它们
them in real time, and finally,
进行实时编辑  最后
verification is just done by
只需把 TVML 属性
copying the TVML properties out
复制出来并粘贴
and restarting your JavaScript
然后直接重启整个 JavaScript
context without doing build and
执行上下文即可  不再需要
run over and over again.
一遍遍地编译并运行
So that is the visual debugging.
以上这就是可视化调试排错
I would like to now move on to
我下面开始介绍
network analysis.
网络分析 (Network Analysis)
Web Inspector now supports
Web 审查器现在支持
looking at all network requests
查看从 TVMLKit
that are sent from TVMLKit
应用发出的所有
application.
网络请求
We will show you individual
我们可以查看
request timing information.
单项请求的耗时信息
So how long a DNS query takes.
比如 DNS 查询花了多长时间
How long a response takes to get
比如响应传输需要花费
sent over the wire.
多长时间
You will inspect the individual
我们还可以审查
request properties that you set
你给某一个请求单独
on your request, so you can
设置的审查属性
verify if these are the exact
可用来确认发出去的信息
things we are sending out.
符合预期
And finally, response and
最后  如果需要
request headers is something you
我们还可以查看响应头
can look at as well.
和请求头
You may have scripts already
可能你目前还写了脚本
today that you use to develop
来内省 LocalStorage
local and session storage.
和 SessionStorage
There is no need to do that
以后这个工作也不需要做了
anymore, because Web Inspector
因为 Web 审查器也会
provides a nice user interface
提供一个很好的 UI
to look at every single key
让我们看到我们 LocalStorage
value pass that is in your local
和 SessionStorage 里每一个
and session storage, and because
关键值路径
you can look at them, it also
而能查看这些数据  也就意味着
means you can modify them.
我们可以进行修改
So you can copy them, delete,
可以进行复制  删除
and move them around.
也可以随意移动
With that, that is TVMLKit and
就这些  这就是 TVMLKit
Web Inspector support, and that
如何支持 Web 审查器
is also how you achieve
这就是如何在开发中获得
happiness.
幸福
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
So what we've seen today,
总结下  我们今天讲了什么
TVMLKit supports RTL right out
首先 TVMLKit 自身  对于所有默认模版
of the box for all default
都提供对从右往左书写语言
templates.
的支持
It is a little bit of work if
如果你的应用程序中有自定义样式
you have custom styles, but it
可能配置起来会复杂一点
is easy to do.
但都很简单
Use data binding and prototypes
像 Parry 讲的  如果你想要流畅
if you want buttery smooth
顺滑的滚动用户体验
scrolling, like Parry has said,
请使用数据绑定和原型
and finally, use Web Inspector
最后  如果你希望在
if you want to reduce the amount
开发应用程序时
of development time it takes to
减少调试排错的时间  请使用
fix bugs.
Web 审查器
For more information, please
更多信息  请访问
visit the following URL.
屏幕上显示的网址
We have sample code and
网站上有样本代码和
documentation that you should
支持文件  都非常有用
really look at.
值得一看
There are amazing sessions, as
另外还有一些 其他很棒的演讲可以参加
well, especially What's New in
尤其 What's New in
tvOS tomorrow.
tvOS tomorrow
Thank you for attending WWDC 17,
感谢大家参加 WWDC 2017
and have a great rest of the
希望大家在大会剩下的时光
conference.
都过得愉快